{
  "scene0025_00": {
    "box": {
      "27": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "White box on the desk",
          "The largest box",
          "The box closest to the windowsill"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the largest box?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the largest box close to the door?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Consider the white box on the desk, is it larger or smaller than the other box nearby?",
            "answer": "Larger",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "29": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The box between monitors",
          "The black box",
          "The smaller box on the desk"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the box between monitors?",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the black box smaller or larger than the white box?",
            "answer": "Smaller",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the black box far from the telephone?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "keyboard": {
      "34": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "White keyboard",
          "Keyboard close to paper towel roll",
          "Keyboard closest to the windowsill"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a book next to the white keyboard?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the keyboard close to paper towel roll?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the white keyboard near the door?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "30": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Black keyboard",
          "Black keyboard in front of monitor",
          "The keyboard farther from the blinds"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a pillow next to the black keyboard?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the keyboard farther from the blinds?",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the black keyboard close to the paper towel roll?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "table": {
      "9": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "A desk that holds two monitors",
          "The desk closest to the paper towel roll",
          "The smaller desk"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the desk that holds two monitors?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Look at the desk that holds two monitors, is it smaller or larger than the other desk?",
            "answer": "Smaller",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a door next to the smaller desk?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "10": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The longest desk",
          "The desk near the larger whiteboard",
          "The desk with boxes on it"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the longest desk?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there any box on the longest desk?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Look at the desk with boxes on it, is it longer or shorter than the other desk?",
            "answer": "Longer",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "blinds": {
      "23": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Blinds opposite the door",
          "Blinds above the windowsill",
          "White blinds"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the blinds above the windowsill?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the white blinds close to the tall shelf?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a door opposite the white blinds?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "cabinet": {
      "38": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The file cabinet under the small whiteboard",
          "The file cabinet in front of the large shelf",
          "The file cabinet opposite the larger whiteboard"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is 'the file cabinet under the small whiteboard'?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the file cabinet in front of the large shelf' near the window?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is above 'the file cabinet in front of the large shelf'?",
            "answer": "Whiteboard",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "15": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The cabinet under the big whiteboard",
          "The cabinet closest to the pillow",
          "The cabinet opposite the small whiteboard"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is 'the cabinet under the big whiteboard'?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the cabinet opposite the small whiteboard' next to the couch?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is above 'the cabinet closest to the pillow'?",
            "answer": "Whiteboard",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "17": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "File cabinet under the big desk",
          "The file cabinet closest to the white trash can",
          "The large file cabinet under monitor"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is 'the file cabinet under the big desk' black?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the small object beside 'the file cabinet under the big desk'?",
            "answer": "Trash can",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the file cabinet closest to the white trash can' taller than the desk?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "16": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The cabinet closest to the blinds",
          "The cabinet under the window",
          "The cabinet farthest from the door"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is 'the cabinet closest to the blinds' black?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the cabinet under the window' near books?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the cabinet under the window' taller or shorter than the desk?",
            "answer": "Taller",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "pillow": {
      "41": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "pillow near the door",
          "pillow below the large whiteboard",
          "pillow opposite the fan"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is 'the pillow near the door' red?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a plant next to 'the pillow below the large whiteboard'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the pillow opposite the fan' close to the door?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "monitor": {
      "0": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The monitor closest to the windowsill",
          "The monitor closest to the blinds",
          "The monitor with brown frame"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a cup next to 'the monitor closest to the windowsill'?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Does 'the monitor closest to the blinds' have a white frame?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the monitor with brown frame' taller or shorter than the adjacent monitor?",
            "answer": "Taller",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "1": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The monitor with white frame on the smaller desk",
          "The monitor behind black keyboard on the smaller desk",
          "The monitor on the smaller desk and farther from the white keyboard"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Look at the monitor behind black keyboard on the smaller desk, what color is its frame?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the monitor with white frame on the smaller desk' next to a white keyboard?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the monitor with white frame on the smaller desk' taller or lower than the adjacent monitor?",
            "answer": "Lower",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "fan": {
      "39": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "black fan",
          "fan on the ground",
          "the fan in front of couch"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the black fan close to the window?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the fan on the ground?",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the black fan taller or shorter than the nearby shelf?",
            "answer": "Shorter",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "chair": {
      "12": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The office chair beside the larger desk",
          "The office chair pushed into desk",
          "The office chair at the same side with the larger whiteboard"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the office chair pushed into desk?",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a refrigerator next to 'the office chair beside the larger desk'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is closer to 'the office chair beside the larger desk', window or door?",
            "answer": "Window",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "13": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The office chair beside the smaller desk",
          "The office chair close to the white keyboard",
          "The office chair oriented towards the door"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the office chair beside the smaller desk?",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the office chair oriented towards the door' close to the door?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a white keyboard next to 'the office chair oriented towards the door'?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "toilet paper": {
      "35": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "white paper towel roll",
          "paper towel roll next to the black shelf",
          "paper towel roll next to the windowsill"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a keyboard next to the white paper towel roll?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is 'the paper towel roll next to the black shelf'?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the white paper towel roll next to the black shelf?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "cup": {
      "32": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "red cup",
          "the cup closer to the monitor",
          "the taller cup"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the taller cup?",
            "answer": "Red",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the red cup taller or shorter than the white cup?",
            "answer": "Taller",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the red cup closer to the monitor than the white cup?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "31": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "White cup",
          "The cup closer to the chair",
          "The shorter cup"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the white cup closer to the monitor than the red cup?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the cup closer to the chair?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the white cup taller or shorter than the red cup?",
            "answer": "Shorter",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "shelf": {
      "36": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The shelf closest to the blinds",
          "The shelf near the windowsill",
          "The short black shelf"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is 'the shelf near the windowsill' taller or shorter than the white shelf?",
            "answer": "Shorter",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the shelf near the windowsill?",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a trash can next to the short black shelf?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "11": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The shelf next to the door",
          "The tall white shelf",
          "The shelf next to a couch"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the shelf next to the door?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the shelf next to the door' taller or shorter than the other shelf?",
            "answer": "Taller",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the tall white shelf far from the door?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "trash can": {
      "19": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "blue trash bin",
          "the trash bin closest to the small whiteboard",
          "the rectangular trash bin"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What shape is the blue trash bin?",
            "answer": "Rectangular",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the trash bin closest to the small whiteboard?",
            "answer": "Blue",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there any other trash bin next to blue trash bin?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "18": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The white trash bin outside the desk",
          "The round trash can outside the desk",
          "The white trash can closest to the door"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the round trash can outside the desk?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What shape is the white trash can closest to the door?",
            "answer": "Round",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a plant next to 'the white trash can closest to the door'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "door": {
      "7": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "door next to the tall shelf",
          "large brown door",
          "the door opposite the windowsill"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the door next to the tall shelf?",
            "answer": "Brown",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the large brown door wider or shorter than the blinds?",
            "answer": "Shorter",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a shelf next to the large brown door?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "headphones": {
      "33": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Headphones on the small desk",
          "Headphones next to a black keyboard",
          "Black headphones under a monitor"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color are the headphones on the small desk?",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a keyboard next to 'the headphones on the small desk'?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What is above 'the headphones next to a black keyboard'?",
            "answer": "Monitor",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "couch": {
      "3": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The sofa opposite the large whiteboard",
          "The sofa near the fan",
          "The sofa next to the tall shelf"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the sofa near the fan?",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a refrigerator beside 'the sofa near the fan'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the sofa opposite the large whiteboard' next to the fan?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "4": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Couch with white pillow",
          "The couch under the large whiteboard",
          "The couch opposite the fan"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the couch with white pillow?",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the couch under the large whiteboard' close to window?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is on 'the couch opposite the fan'?",
            "answer": "White pillow",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "telephone": {
      "28": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Phone on a big box",
          "White telephone",
          "Phone beside a monitor"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the phone on a big box?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the white telephone close to monitor?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the white telephone placed on?",
            "answer": "Box",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    }
  }
}
